Outro eighteen
We'll check it oh yeah
Yeah fur con
Hey, if you wanna win, you gotta play smart
Imagine if the chance the wise will take it all
Let me see how it's gonna dry
So I can't see you're the good
I'm going to run away from the world's thoughts
I'm going to take away from the moment
You're right, when all is good
You're right, it's gonna break
Time消して時はもう満ちた
We're starting, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Brought the glory, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
So 結晶とした光を今こそ解放する
We're starting, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
Brought the glory, oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah
So 逆戦闘 栄光のそう
Happy skill, your運命 will hide me all and all
To be continued...
I understand your frustration, but he can't keep that up forever, so you mustn't worry yourself.
Holy G-Cups! How is anybody supposed to concentrate around those things?
I mean, I know I'm not sporting salad plates, but she's got me beat in looks and experience.
Aw, being a wannabe big shot is getting old. I just want to take control of Kea Brundi and be more like you.
I may have a high rank, but you shouldn't want to be me.
Don't be so modest. You're perfect. You're Aria Doa, the super veteran saver extraordinaire.
You've summoned heroes to like 300 worlds and saved them all!
Not quite. Unfortunately, there was one I couldn't save.
Well, one out of 300 is still incredible. I could totally live with that ratio.
But they can't, Rista. The people who lived on that world? Many lost their lives. We can't afford that kind of mistake.
Yeah, you're right about that. But you know what I mean.
It was just a difficulty level B world, so the mission should have been very easy for me to complete. And yet, I still made a crucial error.
You tried, and, uh...
Oh, forgive me for bringing the mood down. I'm going to fetch us more tea. Would you like some?
Yes, please. That sounds good.
So this is where you've been hiding.
Hey! So I can't walk in on you, but, uh, you can do it to me?
Look! You see what you've done by startling poor Aria?
He's fine. I mean, I'm fine.
Is she a chump for his looks, too? Stupid womanizer. No worse goddessizer.
Hello. You must be the hero that Rista summoned here.
And you are?
My name is Aria. I'm the goddess of the seal, Aria Doa.
You appear to be in quite a hurry. Is something the matter?
I've been exercising to boost my level, but as hard as I try, I can't get it up.
Yes! He's hit a wall on working out!
You shouldn't worry. That kind of thing actually happens to a lot of guys, Seiya.
It's time you stop beating on yourself and start beating the monsters.
Combat? I don't know. It sounds awfully risky, if you ask me.
It's like a hero's entire job description, so...
You know, instead of all that, how about you make me some dumbbells and stuff to help me get swole?
You've got to be kidding me, Seiya! That is not the problem!
You need to go out and get some experience or you're gonna hit the wall again!
Well, what do you suggest I do?
First, clean out your ears and then go find some creepy crawlies!
Oh, I have an idea. What do you think about having one of the gods in the Unified Define Realm help you out with some training exercises?
No disrespect, Aria, but that sounds like a crazy idea!
If he's going up against gods, there's no risk of getting killed.
And he'll gain more XP than from fighting small monsters.
It's my backdoor loophole.
I do like the aspect of minimizing the risk.
Aria, come here, Seiya!
Huh?
Are you sure you can promise him that?
I didn't know that gods were even allowed to take part in training.
It doesn't bother me.
And I'll also double-check with Ishtar to make sure there's no problem.
That's great.
But who's gonna do the actual work?
Neither of us knows a thing about fighting.
I'm a healing goddess and you're a goddess of the seal.
We're both clueless.
It just so happens that I'm looking at a god training his heart out right over there.
Huh?
Him?
He kind of disrupts the whole serenity vibe.
But he refuses to go and swing that thing somewhere else.
He's stubborn divinely, as Cercius.
Yes, but perhaps he'll be persuaded to help us.
This isn't adventure or saving a world.
You're working hard as ever, Cercius.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't Aria, Doa, and Ristarte, and kiddle, uh...
I'm guessing that you're a human?
You must be a hero they summoned.
Look here.
It's not a good idea for a human to go walking around the unified divine realm,
even if you've been invited.
Cercius, we've come to ask you if you would train this hero for us.
Since you're such a high-ranking goddess,
I suppose I have no choice but to honor your requests.
But still...
Listen up, human.
I need to warn you that my training is very intense.
I have serious doubts anyone but a god would be able to handle it.
Yeah.
We'll just see if you're still this cocky after we spar, bro.
You'll be too busy crying like a little girl to talk smack.
What?
You're gonna eat those words, you emo-looking piece of diaper bait?
Just shut up so we can get going.
Huh?
Uh, yeah, with pleasure.
What, the realm's his cock?
Whoa!
Saya's already got him on the defensive.
I just hope his mouth hasn't written a check his butt can't cash.
Cercius the Divine Blade isn't some low-level nobody.
His training sush may be a lesson in humility.
Not necessarily a bad thing for a hero.
First off, why don't you show me what you can do?
So you can keep up with me for a few seconds, at least.
I'm worried about Saya, but if I go over there and check on him,
I know that he's just gonna moan about it.
Oh, Cercius!
So, uh, how's he doing?
Hmm.
For someone who gives so much lip,
he can actually back it up for the most part.
It's impressive.
You don't say.
But he still can't hold a candle to my skills.
Wow!
Some encouraging news for a change.
I know how to pick him.
I'm bored.
What am I supposed to do all day while Saya's busy with his super special training?
Son of a...
Hey there!
How are things on the old training scene?
Oh, well, uh, just fine, I guess.
Yeah, I'm not totally buying that.
Two days.
That's all it took for that cheeky bastard to build up a terrifying amount of power.
Oh!
That does sound like Saya.
He's got that XP boost skill thing going on for him.
If I went all out, I'd wipe that smug look off his face!
You could, but I think it would go against the rules of the divine realm
if you used your godly power against a human like that.
Yeah.
It might actually be worth breaking the rules if it meant I could win a round.
Huh?
I didn't quite catch that.
Nothing important, really.
I just said he's kind of a decent competitor, is all?
This is getting a little awkward, or is it just me?
Excuse me.
Cerseus.
Have you lost a couple of pounds?
Not on purpose.
Never mind.
So, uh, how has the training been coming along?
Oh, uh, it's not so bad.
Okay, but, like, not so bad in what way?
I'm saying it could be worse.
Okay, forgive me for prying,
but I'm gonna need quite a bit more information than just that.
I summoned him, so he's my risk for-
How about you drop it and let me eat at peace?
Fine! Sorry I asked!
Hear that?
Of course I did. So loud.
No, uh, I'm sorry.
The big guy was looking kind of sickly yesterday.
I wonder if he's taking the day off or something.
I'll deliver these snacks and check in on Seiya while I'm at it.
Don't mind me.
I'm just sneaking in to get some nori for my rice balls.
Help yourself.
Get the nori, get the nori for my balls.
Ah!
Oh, Circeus?
Shh, keep it down.
Is something the matter?
Because it kind of looks like you're hiding under there.
It looks that way because it is that way.
You need to listen carefully, okay?
This guy, your hero, nut job.
It's true. I'm well aware.
I told him that he's done enough training, but he says,
nope, not yet. That's all he ever says, and he won't let me go.
He's relentless. I haven't had a chance to rest.
That explains a lot, honestly.
I even told him that he had gotten three times stronger than me,
but he won't stop till he's a hundred times stronger.
It's insane. That guy's a berserker.
No, a berserker probably has more of a heart than him.
He's, he's like a super berserker!
This is where you've been hiding.
I said that you could go and eat lunch,
but it doesn't look like you're eating to me.
Oh, sorry. I can explain.
I, uh, was impersonating nori.
Yeah.
That might be the stupidest thing I've ever heard.
Oh, yeah? You're done now, right?
Not yet. I clearly have more work to do.
I'm more like Wilted Seaweed at this point, sir.
We've wasted too much time already,
so we're gonna have to power through with no more breaks.
No breaks at all?
Sorry, sir, but I'm spent. Please.
No!
He's lost it!
I hate this sword!
I never want to see it again!
The Divine Blade really hates his sword!
I can't even stand and look at those damn hard,
pointy things anymore!
He's still talking about swords, right?
I despise them!
Somebody help me!
Wait!
Seiya!
He doesn't want to do this!
I've been looking for you, Rista.
Ishtar wants to have a word with you.
Hmm? Seriously?
I don't know about what,
but I'm sure it's important.
I'm really, really sorry, Circeus,
but I gotta go now.
Just step it out a little longer!
No, wait!
Please don't leave me alone with this psychopath!
So, Ristarte,
I understand your hero has been training with one of your fellow gods?
Yes, he has.
But apparently, Circeus has decided to just give up.
In all honesty,
he's having a full-blown meltdown over it.
Hmm.
Not too surprising.
Circeus used to be quite a faint-hearted man.
Huh?
Hold on!
Are you telling me that he's a reincarnated human?
I mean,
I always just kind of took it for granted
that he was born a god.
No, in fact,
he was once a human swordsman.
Of course,
when he was reborn,
he lost all memories of his former life.
But those feelings etched deeply into the soul,
they do have a habit of being persistent.
After having such harsh demands wear him down,
it seems that the weaker part of his soul
was exposed somewhat.
In that regard,
one could argue that the experience
has been good for him.
Things can have a strange way of working out.
Say I wasn't the one being trained after all.
Enough about them.
Let's get to the real reason I asked you to come here.
I need you to travel on to the next town immediately.
The next town?
Has something else happened on Kea Brande?
The village I chose for you as a starting point
was a relatively safe place at the time.
However,
the Demon Lord was aware of our plans
and sent a powerful enemy to greet you.
And now,
I can sense that the next village
is in imminent danger of attack as well.
Why does it seem like
every time she looks into the future,
it's something bad?
There will be some very important allies
anxiously waiting on your hero's arrival
in the town of Seymour.
Really?
I wasn't expecting that.
It's true.
So I ask that you hurry to meet up with them.
Do you think you could do that for me, Rista?
Yes, of course!
I'll get right on it!
Okay, no matter what kind of stink he raises,
we are going and that's final!
Guards, your boys!
We're going to get him, Randy!
Ah!
Why are you going full primate on him?
You need to cut that crap out right now!
I didn't ask for your opinion on my technique.
It's part of the training anyway.
Yeah?
Well, color me surprised.
This is what you guys do?
You train him on your back like that?
Why is he just laying there sobbing
and not saying anything?
You need something or what?
Yeah, in fact, I do.
Gaea Brande is in immediate danger.
So stop whatever you're doing here
because we're going right now!
Whatever.
Fine with me.
I think I've gotten all I can out of this guy anyway.
I am perfectly prepared.
That's right.
I'm 100% ready for this.
Great.
But first...
Apologize to Cersei as before the trauma fully sets in!
Okay, this town is called Samal.
According to Ishtar,
we have allies waiting for us at the church,
so let's get over to them.
Everyone hold on what you can!
Hold on a second, please!
Is something happening?
Crane Castle to the northwest has fallen.
This town's about to be flooded with the undead.
You should just keep on moving, lady.
So, what are the undead?
Obviously, they're dead things that can move and attack.
Like zombies, for instance.
They're pretty hard to beat with just swords.
Well, then how do you kill them, Rista?
Fire spells and splashing them with holy water is good, too.
Ah, holy water.
Holy water.
If you're dealing with those undead,
you'll need to get yourself some of that.
So glad your shopkeepers are still around.
We can't let the undead keep us from making a living.
You'll need all you can carry,
because you don't want to run out.
You're right about that.
I'll take a thousand.
Hey, buddy, I know you said you don't want to run out,
but this is overkill.
I mean, you just got to splash a little bit on each one of them.
You're not going to be dunking them in this stuff or anything, you know?
That's the reason it comes in those tiny little vials.
I don't think you could carry that many on you.
Even if you could, the weight would definitely slow you down.
And besides,
I don't have anywhere close to a thousand of those vials in stock today.
Well, then you better order some right now,
because if not, I'm going to tear out that ascob, brosom.
Well, just take ten!
It's not enough.
It is, too.
Besides, I'm starting to sense those undead guys getting closer.
We've got to hurry and meet our friends at the church.
Huh.
They'd better make it worth our time.
Listen, when I talk about meeting our friends,
you're supposed to get all hyped up.
Please, don't be a jerk.
Oh, who's there?
My stars.
You're a goddess, aren't you?
You must be.
There was a sign from God that you are coming,
so we've been anxiously awaiting your arrival ever since then.
These two are descendants from Dragonkin,
which means they have dragon blood in their veins.
They will be teaming up with our hero,
and together they'll defeat the Demon Lord.
Dragonkin descendants.
Exactly the kind of allies we want.
Greetings, brave hero.
Let me introduce myself.
I'm Father Marth, pleased to make your acquaintance.
Hey, what are you doing that for?
That stuff's for the bad guys!
Oh, father!
Sayah!
Hang on, doesn't that only happen when it's used on undead creatures?
Crazy.
So the hero was able to tell he was one?
That's totally amazing!
I should have expected the one who killed Chaos Machina to be so cunning.
My plan was to slaughter the lot of you once I gained your trust,
but this changes things!
No matter.
I can still wipe out all of you in one fell swoop.
My undead power was bestowed on me by Death Magla,
one of the Demon Lord's four heavenly kings!
And now I shall use it to destroy you!
Bring it on, you bastard!
Yeah!
You gotta deal with me, too!
How long has Father Stinkmouth been at this church?
Uh, he came over as a missionary from Crane Castle just a couple of days ago.
I see.
So this dude's not one of the local townspeople.
What are you doing?
Get over there and help our friends make him dead again!
You don't have to yell.
For your information, I've already immobilized the enemy.
What's happening?
Look at that.
Even when I tear you apart, you don't bleed.
You just sound constipated.
Are they all like you?
When the hell'd you cut him up?
I didn't even see you draw your sword!
I never saw him use his sword, either.
Maybe whatever he was doing with Circeus was actually training.
But what I really don't get...
Hey, how could you tell he was one of those undeads, anyway?
I used my brain.
Duh.
So, like, how did you use it?
The priest was the oldest and most feeble person here.
He'd be dead soonest, which means he'd also be undead soonest.
So I gave him a little shower.
You're saying you used logic and reasoning to destroy him.
I don't get it!
That wasn't logical at all!
Oh, isn't our little hero so damn clever
while Deathmogla's undead army is gonna come put an end
to your stupid victory celebration?
Huh?
I'm not talking about just a couple of zombies.
Tomorrow morning, there'll be 10,000 ready to eat your brains for breakfast.
10,000 undead coming?
And they'll be here by the morning?
Yeah.
Thanks for translating everything that we literally just heard, genius.
I'm going to need to clean this mess up.
Since cutting you up didn't shut you up,
I'll have to be extra thorough.
Everyone run!
But why?
What's he doing?
Yes, Ron, trust me!
Maximum Inferno!
Then there we go!
He always goes overboard on the cleanup of the finest like an afterthought.
Is cleanup even the right word?
He just blew it up.
The historic church of Seymol has been reduced to rubble.
You're welcome, sister.
I single-handedly saved all of you for free.
Yeah, because you wiped out the whole church!
And the poor nun probably just died from the shock!
That's one way to do it.
This guy's pretty weird.
But lucky for us, he's super strong.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Hero.
My name's Mosh.
I'm a warrior with dragonkin blood.
And I'm Elulu.
I've known Mosh since we were both little kids.
I'm a mage, and I also have dragonkin blood in me.
How about we all work together, okay?
What's your name, Mr. Hero?
Seiya.
Seiya Ryuun.
This one's human.
What are you doing?
Him too.
Cool.
Human.
Probably not a good idea while she's unconscious.
Hey!
What did you pour it on me for?
I had to be sure you hadn't turned undead at some point.
Yeah, why?
This guy's got a trust issue.
More like a problem.
Huh?
Hey, why are you staring like that?
Yeah, what's the deal?
You're being super creepy all of a sudden.
If these two are supposed to be our allies on this adventure,
we got to see those stats.
This isn't what goddesses and heroes do!
You're really scaring me!
Not all that impressive, to be honest.
They don't have a fraction of what Seiya's packing.
But I guess they have room to grow.
It'll be nice to have these guys on the team, don't you think?
No way.
But they have dragonkin blood,
so once they go through all the steps and learn dragon metamorphosis,
they'll be fine!
No way.
Let's go.